Hi! I am Ivan, UI/UX developer.

I am 21 years old guy, currently educating myself in the field of front-end development. I do so trough multiple online certifications. I was studying in Copenhagen but my country of origin is Slovakia. I treat digital world as my passion and future.







il.ivanlesko@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Digital consultant 0 3/2020 - presence

> Web development, UI/UX, Content creation, wireframing, SEO, testing, branding

Communication director, Gjarfest O 2017-2020

> Communication, social media, content creation, ideation, event management

Agency intern, Hejdude.sk 0 1/2020-5/2020

> Graphic design, e-mail templates, keyword research, content creation, SEO

EDUCATION

KEA, multimedia design 0 2020-2022

> UI/UX, web development, content, communication

University Presov, digital marketing 2019-2020

> Marketing, digital marketing, business, economics

GJAR, gymnasium O 2015-2019

> General studies with emphasis on languages

FEATURES



QUICK LEARNER

I am able to understand and learn new concepts fairly quickly



DIGITAL CROSOVER

I have knowledge from various fields web development, UI/UX, marketing



CHALLENGE SEEKER

It is in my nature to constantly look for new challenges

SKILLS

















HOBBIES

The biggest hobby of mine is playing drums. Besides music, I am generally involved in arts. If I want to really rest my mind I tend to do sports, mostly basketball, gym and skiing. I train my creativity in the kitchen. I am a passionate home-cook and fan of Asian cuisine.